Vinod Kumar Bhavana

Fullstack Developer

Fullstack Developer with 4 years of IT experience in the design, development, and implementing of client and server side applications using HTML, CSS, Javascript, Angular, React, Ionic, Node.js, MongoDB and SQL as databases.

Centific Global Technologies India Private Limited

□ Web API development in ASP.NET core, C# & NodeJs with Typescript.

User interface design and development with React.js.

Julius66 Software India Private Limited

Built RESTful API's using Node.js and Express.js.

State management in Angular using RxJS.

back-end components, enhancing application functionality

Worked on optimising Angular performance by Lazy-Loading.

A Saas based product that utilizes Fullstack development(React, .Net, Node) is structured using

Worked with Cypress unit test framework to write unit tests for front-end components.

Extensively used Git for version controlling and regularly pushed the code to GitHub. Used JIRA as the bug tracking system to track and maintain the history of bugs/issues on

Created custom Directives, Pipes and Reusable components for better usability.

Good knowledge in MongoDB curd operations, lookups and aggregations.

Built Hybrid applications using Ionic framework for IOS and Android platforms.

micro-services architecture and integrated via GraphQL to create a suitable product for the end

Developed web services and APIs that enabled seamless communication between front-end and

Hyderabad, India

Hyderabad, India

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fullstack Developer

02/2022 - Present

Roles and Responsibilities:

everyday basis.

07/2019 - 02/2022

Roles and Responsibilities:

Intermediate Developer



v.bhavana777@gmail.com



9885448635



Ongole, India



linkedin.com/in/bhavanavinod-kumar-1b6799211

SKILLS

CSS

SOL

LANGUAGES

English















EDUCATION

BSc

S.S.N College, Ongole

03/2013 - 03/2016

Course

MEC's

INTERESTS ACHIEVEMENTS

Learn new technologies.

Won the Codeburst game for 2 times in my organization.

Star performer of the year 2022

Play Cricket

Listen to music